

agrawalmahima04@gmail.com



SKILLS

Social Media Management

Copy Writing

SEO Content Writer

Keyword Reasearch

Adobe Photoshop

Client Acquisition

INTERESTS

Freelance Writing

Creative Designing

Fictional Reading

Social Media Fanatic

CERTIFICATIONS

Digital Marketing Udemy 2021

Adobe Photoshop SRIIT Computers

N.H. Goel Finishing School Raipur

Mahima Agrawal

CONTENT WRITER

ABOUT ME

Having the most preeminence and keenness in content writing with an experience of more than two years; having articulacy in blogs, articles, websites, and ad content. Also, a result-oriented Social Media Marketer having experience in the field with Konsole Indya where have successfully driven various marketing campaigns and acquired customers through online activities; efficiently grasping the idea of SEO and Creative Content Writing while handling Social Media profiles of various clients. Also acknowledged in Customer Acquisition and Relationship Management through The ISO Consult and CII Chhattisgarh.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Writer Raipur / Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Working in Alco Foods was a great experience for my pen skills as I gained diligence in blog and article writing along with writing content for ads in email and social media and concise product descriptions for Amazon.

Social Media Trainee Raipur / Apr 2021 - Jun 2022

Konsole gave me great exposure in the field of social media marketing as the job role catered to the social media handling of clients inclusive of conducting Lead Generation Projects and running Marketing Campaigns. Along with giving knowledge of Keyword Research for Amazon and Websites had experience in designing the outlook for websites and product pages.

Marketing Intern Apr 2020 - Aug 2020

My duration of Covid was spent with Remote working for The ISO Consult as a marketing intern with the job role of promoting the company on various social media platforms by creating 30+ impactful posters and videos for the Lead generation project, acquiring customers, and running SMS and email campaigns.

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration Institute of Technology and Management / Raipur / 2021

Bachelor of Business Administration

Maharaja Agrasen International College / Raipur / 2018